Time. All right. Klingons. pencils down.
C'est fini ! Klingons, posez vos crayons.
Okay. I have paid).
J'ai pukh.
ALL: Got it.
Je l'ai.
ALL: Yep.
Oui.
-l have chum. ALL: Got it.
- J'ai chum. - Je l'ai.
ALL: Yeah. -And kreplach.
- Oui. - Et kreplach.
-Hold on a second. kreplach? -Yeah.
- Attends voir, [map/acl) ? - Oui.
That isn't Klingon. It's Yiddish for meat-filled dumpling.
Ça n'est pas klingon. Ça veut dire raviole en yiddish.
Well. as it turns out. it's also a Klingon word.
Il se trouve que c'est aussi un mot klingon.
Really? Define it.
Oui ? Donne la définition.
Kreplach, a hearty Klingon dumpling.
Kreplach, c'est une copieuse raviole klingon.
Judge's ruling?
Décision du jury ?
Hey. guys. I need to use your TV.
Salut, j'ai besoin de votre télé.
What's wrong with your TV?
- Quel est le problème avec la tienne ? - Je ne sais pas. Elle est morte.
Did you pay your cable bill?
Tu as payé la facture ?
Ugh. You sound just like the cable company.
Tu parles comme la compagnie du câble.
All right. so shh.
Tyra Banks est en train de virer quelqu'un dans Le pruchain tap-mudèle.
-Excuse me. Penny. but we're-- -Don't tell her.
- Désolé, mais on était... - Ne lui dis pas.
--p|aying Klingon Boggle.
en train de jouer au Boggle Klingon.
What do you mean. “Ohh?” Like she didn't know we were nerds?
Tu crois qu‘elle ne sait pas qu'on est des intellos ?
All right. if you must watch. then mute it with closed captions. please.
S'il faut vraiment que tu regardes, coupe le son et mets les sous—titres.
Fine.
D'accord.
All right. Boggle warriors.
Bon, les guerriers du Boggle.
Look at those women.
Regardez ces femmes.
They're gorgeous.
Elles sont superbes.
Oh. wall. Nice.
Wall. Joli.
Too bad that's a proper noun.
Dommage, c‘est un nom propre.
Oh. look. there's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
Regarde, la future Mme Wolowitz.
No. wait. that's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
Ou plutôt celle—lè.
With her head in the lap of--
Sa tête est sur les genoux de...
What a coincidence. It's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
Quelle coincidence ! Voici la future Mme Wolowitz.
Yeah. and they can all move in with you and your mother.
Oui, elles vont toutes emménager avec toi chez ta mère.
The current Mrs. Wolowitz.
L'actuelle Mme Wolowitz.
ls quchbe spelled with a “qou or a “ko?“
Est-ce que quchbe s‘écrit avec un... ou un...
Why is that Mrs. Wolowitz crying?
Pourquoi Mme Wolowitz pleure-t-elle ?
Oh. that's Anai's. None of the other girls in the house like her.
C‘est Anaïs. Personne ne l'aime dans la maison.
House? What house?
Une maison ? Quelle maison ?
-They all live in a house together. -A house? Where?
- Elles vivent ensemble dans une maison. - Une maison ? Où ça ?
ldon't know. Somewhere in LA.
Je sais pas. Quelque part à LA.
Wait a minute.
Attends voir.
You're telling me that I'm within driving distance...
Tu veux dire que je suis a deux pas
...of a house filled with aspiring supermodels?
d‘une maison remplie de futurs top—modéles ?
Yeah. I guess.
Je crois.
And they live together and shower together...
Elles vivent ensemble, se douchent ensemble,
...and have naked pillow fights?
font des batailles de polochons a poil ?
-Hey. where are you going? -To pay my cable bill.
- Où tu vas ? - Je vais payer ma facture de câble.
All right. pencils down.
Posez VOS crayons.
l have laid), Ina/(h...
J ' ai Iukh, mah/r
...and chain/(h. Anybody got those?
et chain/rh. Quelqu'un les a ?
Did I miss anything? Did they kick Giselle off?
J'ai loupé quelque chose ? Est-ce qu‘ils ont viré Giselle ?
Not yet. but her underwater photo shoot was an embarrassment.
Pas encore, mais la séance photo sous l‘eau a été une galère.
Sadly. Mrs. Giselle Wolowitz is sensitive to chlorine.
Mme Giselle Wolowitz est sensible au chlore.
Lucky for her I like my fashion models pruny and bug-eyed.
Heureusement pour elle, j‘aime la peau fripée et les yeux globuleux.
Sheldon. the food's here.
Sheldon, le repas est servi.
Oh. there's the house.
C‘est la maison.
Freeze frame. freeze frame.
Mets sur pause !
-What are you doing? -Marking the positions and landmarks...
- Que tais—tu ? - Je marque les positions et les repères,
...so we can find the house of the supermodels.
pour qu'on retrouve la maison des top-modèles.
-Why? -|sn't it obvious?
- Pourquoi ? - Tu ne devines pas ?
Every week they kick out a beautiful girl...
Ils virent un canon toutes les semaines.
...making her feel unwanted and without self-esteem.
Elle se sent alors de trop et perd son amour—propre.
A.k.a. the future Mrs. Howard Wolowitz.
En gros, c‘est la future Mme Wolowitz.
-|s my hamburger medium-well? -Yes.
- Mon hamburger est a point ? - Oui.
-Di|| slices. not sweet?
Cornichons non sucrés ?
-|ndividua| relish packets? Onion rings? -Yes.
Sachets de condiments individuels ? Oignons frits ?
-Extra breading? What did they say? -| asked. No.
- Du pain en plus ? - J'ai demandé, mais non.
-Did you protest? Vociferously? -Yes. No.
Tu as protesté ? Avec véhémence ?
Well. then. what took you so long?
Pourquoi tu as mis tant de temps alors ?
Just eat.
Mange.
-Hey. guys. What'd I miss. what'd I miss? -Giselle's hanging by a thread.
- Qu'est-ce que j'ai loupé ? - Giselle est a deux doigts de partir.
Oh. good. I hate her.
Tant mieux, je la déteste.
Then you're not invited to our wedding.
Tu n'es pas invitée à notre mariage, alors.
-Here you go. -Thank you.
- Tiens. - Merci.
Oh. do we have to suffer...
Faut-il encore qu'on subisse
...through this transparently manipulative. pseudo-reality again?
cette pseudo réalité Visiblement manipulatrice ?
You and l have a standing TV schedule...
On a un programme télévisé régulier,
...the result of extensive debate and compromise.
résultat d'un débat approfondi et consensuel.
Any alterations except for breaking news...
Tout changement, sauf flashs spéciaux,
...have to be pre-approved at the weekly roommate meeting.
doit être pré-approuvé a la réunion hebdomadaire des colocs.
Put it on the agenda.
Mets-Ie à l‘ordre du jour.
You have to make a motion.
Tu dois présenter une motion.
I'll make a motion but you're not gonna like it.
Tu n‘aimeras pas ma motion.
Fine. Mock parliamentary procedure.
Trés bien. Moque-toi des procédures parlementaires.
At least put it on mute.
Coupe le son, au moins.
Oh. Giselle's not getting kicked off.
Ils ne vont pas virer Giselle.
It's totally gonna be Summer.
Ce sera Summer, c‘est sûr.
-What? -Sheldon's onion ring. Just put it back.
- Quoi ? - C‘est a Sheldon. Repose—lé.
-|t's one onion ring. -Just put it back before he comes.
- Je n'en ai pris qu‘un. - Repose, avant qu'il arrive.
Don't think that's where it was.
Il n‘était pas a cet endroit.
Okay. here he comes. Deny. deny. deny. people. Wall of silence.
Le voilà. On réfute. On se tait.
-Who touched my--? -Penny. Penny did it.
- Qui a touché à mon... - C‘est Penny.
Why would you do that?
Pourquoi tu as fait ca ?
I don't know. I was hungry? What's the big deal?
Je ne sais pas. J‘avais faim ? C‘est grave ?
The big deal is that nobody touches food on my plate.
Personne ne touche a ma nourriture dans mon assiette.
All right. I didn't know. I'm sorry.
D‘accord, je ne savais pas. Désolée.
Well. I'm sorry. but that is your second strike.
Je suis désolé, mais c‘est ta deuxiéme faute.
-What? -You have two strikes.
- Quoi ? - Tu as commis deux fautes.
Three strikes and you're out.
Trois fautes et c‘est fini.
It's a sports metaphor.
C‘est une métaphore sportive.
-A sports metaphor? -Yes. baseball.
- Métaphore sportive ? - Du base—bali.
All right. yeah. I'll play along.
Bien, je vais jouer le jeu.
-What was my first strike? -March 18th.
- Quelle était la premiére ? - Le 18 mars.
You violated my rule about forwarding e-mail humor.
Tu m'as transféré un e-mail humoristique.
I did?
J'ai fait ca ?
The photo of the cat who wants to “Has Cheezburger?“
Oui, la photo d'un chat qui dit “moi vouloir cheezeburger“.
Oh. come on. everybody loves Lolcats.
Mais tout le monde aime les Lolcats.
They're cute and they can't spell...
Ils sont mignons. Ils font des fautes,
...because they're cats.
parce que ce sont des chats.
I trusted you with my e-mail address and you betrayed that trust...
Je t'ai confié mon adresse e-mail. Tu as trahi ma confiance
...by sending me Internet banality. Strike one.
en m'envoyant des banalités. Première faute.
Touching my food. strike two.
Puis tu as touché ma nourriture.
Don't worry. they only stay on your record for a year.
Ne t'inquiète pas. Ça ne reste qu'un an sur ton dossier.
You can get them removed early but you have to take his class.
Tu peux les effacer avant en assistant à son cours.
-Oh. come on. I touched one onion ring. -And then you put it back.
- J'ai seulement touché un oignon frit. - Et tu l'as reposé.
Compromising the integrity of all the other onion rings.
Tu compromets ainsi l‘intégrité de tous les autres oignons frits.
Oh. honey. the buses don't go where you live. do they?
Tu ne veux vraiment pas comprendre, hein ?
Look. | wish I could be more lenient with you.
J'aurais bien été plus indulgent avec toi,
But since you've become a permanent member...
mais tu es un membre permanent.
...l've to hold you to the same standards as everybody else.
Donc j'applique les mêmes règles qu'avec tout le monde.
Congratulations. you're officially one of us.
Félicitations, tu es officiellement des nôtres.
[CHANTS] One of us. one of us.
Elle est des nôtres !
Well. what a thrill.
Je suis aux anges.
-You're sitting in my spot. -Oh. gee. you've gotta be kidding me.
- C‘est ma place. - Mais tu plaisantes ou quoi ?
-Leonard. she's in my spot. -Yeah. yeah.
Leonard, c‘est ma place.
See. here's the thing...
Tu sais, quand tu seras partie, il faudra encore que je le supporte.
ldon't care. I'm taking a stand.
Je m'en ﬁche. Je prends position.
Metaphorically.
Métaphoriquement.
All right. that's it.
D‘accord, ça y est.
-Strike three. -Oh. strike three.
- Troisième faute.
l'm banished?
Je suis bannie ?
-What the hell kind of crap is that? LEONARD: Listen.
- C‘est complétement nui. - Écoute.
-Don't worry. I'll talk to him. -Yeah. you do that.
- Ne t'inquiète pas, je lui parlerai. - C‘est ca.
Just so I know. would you be open to taking his class?
Juste pour savoir, tu serais d'accord pour suivre son cours ?
You can do it online.
Tu peux le faire par Internet.
So on our triangulation. we've narrowed the location of the Top Model house...
La maison des Tup-mudèles se situe dans cet espace délimité par ce triangle
...to three square miles in the Hollywood Hills.
de 5 km2 dans les collines d'Hollywood.
Or possibly Durham. North Carolina.
Ou peut-être à Durham, en Caroline du Nord.
When we find it. wanna go with us?
Vous viendrez, une fois trouvée ?
-To do what? -Party with the pretty girls. dude.
- Pour quoi faire ? - Faire la fête avec de jolies ﬁlles, mec.
Are you insane? You're not gonna party with them.
Mais vous êtes fous ? Vous ne pourrez pas faire ca.
You're not even gonna get near that place.
Vous n‘approcherez même pas cet endroit.
That's what they said to Neil Armstrong about the moon.
C‘est aussi ce qu‘ils ont dit a Neil Armstrong a propos de la lune.
No one said anything of the kind to Neil Armstrong.
Personne n‘a jamais dit ca a Neil Armstrong.
The entire nation dedicated a decade of effort and treasure...
La nation entière a consacré dix ans d‘efforts et de fonds
...to put a man on the moon.
pour l‘envoyer sur la lune.
My fellow Americans. before this year is out...
Mes chers compatriotes, avant la fin de l'année,
...we will put a Wolowitz on one of America '5 Top Models.
nous enverrons Wolowitz à l'émission du Prochain tup-mudèle.
And a large number of people will believe it never happened.
Et beaucoup ne croiront pas que c‘est arrivé.
Okay. let me guess.
Laissez—moi deviner.
Ouesadilla with soy cheese...
Quesadilla et fromage de soja
-...for lactose-intolerant Leonard. -Thank you.
- sans lactose, pour Leonard. - Merci.
Shrimp caesar salad with no almonds for the highly allergic...
Salade césar aux crevettes sans amandes pour l'allergique
...kosher-only-on-the-High-Holidays Howard.
qui ne mange cachére que pendant les fêtes, Howard.
And for our suddenly-back-on-the-Hindu-wagon Raj...
Et pour Raj qui est soudainement redevenu hindou,
...meat lover's pizza. no meat.
pizza spéciale Viande, sans Viande.
Coming right up.
Ça arrive tout de suite.
Wait. Excuse me. You forgot my barbecue bacon cheeseburger...
S'il te plait. Tu as oublié mon cheeseburger au bacon sauce barbecue
...barbecue sauce. bacon and cheese on the side.
avec sauce barbecue, bacon et fromage à part.
Oh. I didn't tell you?
Je ne t'ai pas dit ?
You're banished from the Cheesecake Factory.
Tu es banni du restaurant.
-Why? -Well. you have three strikes.
- Pourquoi ? - Tu as commis trois fautes.
One. coming in. Two. sitting down.
Une, entrer. Deux, t‘assoir.
And three. I don't like your attitude.
Et trois, je n'apprécie pas ton attitude.
You can't do that. Not only is it a violation of California State Law...
Tu ne peux pas faire ca. Non seulement, tu enfreins la loi,
...it flies directly in the face of Cheesecake Factory policy.
mais c‘est tout a fait contraire a la politique de ce restaurant.
Yeah. no. there's a new policy: No shoes. no shirt. no Sheldon.
Oui. Il y a une nouvelle règle: sans chaussures, sans t-shirt, sans Sheldon.
I bet we could sell that sign all over Pasadena.
On pourrait vendre cette enseigne dans tout Pasadena.
-Penny. can I talk to you for a minute? -Uh-huh.
Je peux te parler une minute ?
-Hi.
- Salut.
Look. here's the thing.
Écoute.
I talked to Sheldon and he feels terrible.
J'ai parlé a Sheldon et il s'en veut vraiment.
And he agrees that he was unreasonable and out of line.
Il pense aussi que son comportement a été excessif et inapproprié.
-Really? Well. that's great. -Yeah.
- Vraiment ? C‘est génial. - Oui.
Oh. just apologize to him. okay?
Alors, présente—lui tes excuses.
What? I'm not gonna apologize to that nutcase.
Quoi ? Je ne vais pas m‘excuser auprès de ce cinglé.
Come on. it's easy. He'll even tell you what to say.
Allez, c‘est facile. Il te dira même quoi dire.
Don't you get it? You keep going along with his insanity. you're encouraging him.
Vous allez toujours dans son sens. Ça ne fait qu'encourager sa démence.
We're not encouraging. It's more like knuckling under.
On ne l‘encourage pas. On s‘y résigne.
I like hanging out but I'm not gonna apologize for something I didn't do.
J'aime être avec vous, mais je ne m‘excuserai pas
Well. actually. technically you did do it.
En fait, tu l'as fait.
That's strike one. Leonard.
C‘est ta première faute, Leonard.
Here you go. Ouesadilla.
Et voilà. Quesadilla.
Salad.
Salade.
Here's your pizza.
Ta pizza.
And thanks to Sheldon's heated discussion with my manager...
Et après un débat animé avec mon manager,
...barbecue bacon cheeseburger. barbecue sauce. bacon and cheese on the side.
Ie cheeseburger au bacon, sauce barbecue, bacon et fromage à part.
Thank you.
Merci.
Go ahead. Eat it.
Vas-v, mange—lé.
I dare you.
Çhiche !
That's it. There's the house. I found America's top models!
Voilà la maison des top-modéles.
-Are you sure? -Look. On the roof.
- Tu es sûr ? - Regarde !
Anai's and Giselle are sunbathing.
Anaïs et Giselle font bronzette sur le toit.
European style.
Ala mode européenne.
You can recognize people on Google Earth?
Tu reconnais les gens avec Google Earth ?
Of course not. I got a buddy of mine at NORAD to have a spy drone fly over.
Mais non. J'ai un pote au NORAD.
NORAD? You're using military aircraft?
Le NORAD ? Tu as fait appel à l‘armée de l‘air ?
It was already targeted to poke around a nuclear reactor in Siberia.
Il était déja en mission vers la Sibérie pour s‘occuper d'un réacteur nucléaire.
I took it an hour out of its way. tops.
Ça lui a pris une heure de plus, maximum.
Okay. where is he?
Il est où ?
Sheldon? I dropped him off at the comic book store.
Qui ? Sheldon ? Je l'ai déposé a la librairie.
Here. Try and go online.
Essaie de te connecter a Internet.
-Prob|em with the Wi-Fi? -No. just try.
- Un problème de Wi-Fi ? - Essaie.
Greetings, hamburger-luncher.
Chère tuucheuse de hamburger.
You are probably wondering why you cannot [M with your little friends...
Tu le demandes sûrement pourquoi tu ne peux pas discuter avec les amis.
...ahout how much you heart various things.
Au sujet de les passions.
Well, this recorded message is alerting you...
Cet enregistrement a pour but de te prévenir
...that I am putting an end to your parasitic piggybacking upon our Wi-Fi.
que je mets [in a‘ ton usage illicite de notre connexion Wi—Fi.
I! you want to remedy the situation...
Pour remédier a‘ la Situation,
...you can contact the phone company, set up your own Wi-Fi and pay for it...
tu peux contacter la compagnie, faire installer et payer ton propre Wi—Fi,
...or you may apologize to me.
ou alors me présenter des excuses.
-Well? -| reiterate. Knuckle under.
- Alors ? - Je te l'ai déja dit. Résigne-toi.
Oh. no. no. no. It is on.
Il n‘est en pas question.
I'm gonna introduce your friend to a world of hurt.
Je vais le faire souffrir.
Oh. Penny. you don't wanna get into it with Sheldon.
Tu ne devrais pas jouer a ca avec lui.
The guy's one lab accident away from being a super villain.
Un accident de labo de plus et il se transforme en super méchant.
ldon't care. l was in junior rodeo. I can hogtie and castrate him in 60 seconds.
Je m'en fous. J'ai fait du rodéo. Je le ligote et le castre en 60 secondes.
No need to neuter the nerd. I can get you back online.
Pas la peine de le châtrer. Je te remettrai ton Internet.
There. see?
Tu vois ?
Problem solved.
Problème résolu.
SHELDON: Hello, puny insects.
Salut, petits microbes.
As a consequence of your efforts to circumvent my will...
Suite a‘ vos efforts pour contourner ma volonté,
...everyone is awarded one additional strike.
vous avez tous une faute de plus au compteur.
Thanks a lot. Howard.
Merci beaucoup, Howard.
What are you complaining about? I'm the one who has to take the class again.
De quoi tu te plains ? Ce n‘est pas toi qui doit encore suivre son cours.
Hello.
Bonjour.
Time to do your laundry. huh?
C‘est l‘heure de la lessive ?
Saturday night.
On est samedi soir.
Saturday is laundry night.
Ça veut dire lessive.
I know.
Je sais.
Every Saturday at 8:15.
Tous les samedis, à 20h15.
Easy to anticipate.
Facile à prévoir.
SHELDON: What are you implying?
Qu'est-ce que tu insinues ?
l'm implying that you're a creature of habit.
J‘insinue que tu es routinier.
And if something were to prevent you...
Et si quelque chose t'empêche de faire ta lessive a 20h15,
...you might find it...
tu trouveras ca
...unpleasant.
désagréable.
Knuckle under. my ass.
Me résigner ? Tu peux toujours courir !
Are all the machines taken?
Toutes les machines sont utilisées ?
What are you gonna do?
Comment tu vas faire ?
No problem.
C‘est pas grave.
I'll just do my laundry another night.
Je ferai ma lessive un autre soir.
Another night?
Un autre soir ?
Well. I guess you can try...
Tu peux toujours essayer.
...but deep inside your heart you'll know...
Mais au fond de toi, tu sais très bien que samedi soir, c‘est le soir de la lessive.
Woman. you are playing with forces beyond your ken.
Tu joues avec des forces qui dépassent ton entendement.
Yeah. well. your Ken can kiss my Barbie.
Et toi, va jouer aux billes.
Where are my clothes?
Où sont mes vêtements ?
-Your clothes? -Yes. I left them in the washers.
- Tes vêtements ? - Ils étaient dans la machine.
I went to get them. they were gone.
Ils n‘y sont plus.
Really? Despite the sign that says: “Do not leave laundry unattended“?
Ah bon ? Malgré le panneau qui dit :
Sheldon. where are my clothes?
Où sont mes vêtements ?
You know. I do recall seeing some female undergarments.
Je me souviens avoir vu des dessous féminins.
Where was that? Oh. yes.
Où était-ce ? Je sais !
Earlier this evening...
Tout a l'heure,
...I happened to gaze out the window and a brassiere caught my eye.
je regardais parla fenétre quand une brassiére a attiré mon attention.
Do those look familiar?
Ça te dit quelque chose ?
How the hell did you get them up on that telephone wire?
Comment tu as fait pour les pendre a ce câble téléphonique ?
When you understand the laws of physics. Penny. anything is possible.
Quand tu connais les lois dela physique, rien n‘est impossible.
And may I add: Mua-ha-ha.
Et j‘ajouterai :
-Get them down. -Apo|ogize.
- Décroche-les. - Excuse-toi.
-Never. -Then I suggest...
- Jamais. - Je te suggère
...you get a very long stick and play panty piﬁata.
de trouver un long bâton et de jouer a la piñata.
Look. wait. Sheldon.
Attends.
This has gotten out of hand. Okay.
C‘est allé trop loin.
I've done some stupid things. you've done some stupid things.
J'ai été stupide, tu as été stupide.
How about call it even. move on with our lives?
Et si on passait à autre chose ?
I've done no stupid things.
Tu as été stupide, pas moi.
-Look. you gotta meet me halfway here. -I am.
- Il faut un effort mutuel. - Je le fais déja.
I'm willing to concede that you've done some stupid things.
Je reconnais que tu as été stupide.
Hey. you guys are talking again. Good.
Vous vous reparlez ? Cool.
What happened?
Qu'est-ce qui s‘est passé ?
Leonard. remember when I said it was on?
Je t‘avais parlé de rodéo. Je crois que c‘est l'heure.
Oh. not junior rodeo.
Non, pas le rodéo.
What did you do?
Qu'est-ce que tu as fait ?
I had no choice. Leonard. She ruined laundry night.
Je n‘avais pas le choix. Elle a gâché ma séance de lessive.
Telephone wires can't electrocute you. can they?
On peut s'électrocuter avec des câbles téléphoniques ?
No. Look. this has to stop.
Non. Ça a assez duré.
-Oh. no. no. no. It is just beginning. -All right.
- Ce n‘est que le début. - D‘accord.
I really didn't wanna do this...
Je ne voulais pas en arriver la mais...
...but here.
Tiens.
What this?
C‘est quoi ?
Sheldon's kryptonite.
La kryptonite de Sheldon.
Oh. my God.
Mon Dieu.
He can never know that I gave that to you.
Il ne doit jamais savoir que je t'ai donné ca.
Look. I said I wanted to hurt him. but--
J'ai dit que je voulais le blesser.
But this?
Mais ca ?
It will shorten the war by five years and save millions of lives.
Ça raccourcira la guerre de cinq années et sauvera des millions de Vies.
Pause it. That's it. Confirmed.
Mets en pause. C‘est confirmé.
We now have the address of the Top Model house.
On a l‘adresse dela maison des Top-modèles.
God bless you. Google Street View registered trademark.
Dieu bénisse Google Street View.
Okay. for the record. what you are doing is really creepy.
Ce que vous faites est vraiment effrayant.
If it's “creepy“ to use the Internet. military satellites and robot aircraft...
Si c‘est ”effrayant“ d'utiliser Internet,
...to find a house full of gorgeous young models...
pour trouver une maison remplie de top-modéles,
...so that I can drop in on them unexpectedly. then fine. I'm “creepy.“
pour que je puisse leur rendre visite à l‘improviste.
Oh. hi. Yeah. hold on a second. I'll get him.
Bonsoir. Une seconde, je vous le passé.
Sheldon. it's for you.
C‘est pour toi.
-Who is it? -Your mother.
- Qui c‘est ? - Ta mère.
Oh. good.
Ah, bien.
Hi. Mom. How are you?
Salut maman. Comment ca va ?
But. Mom.
Mais, maman.
She keeps sitting in my spot.
Elle n'arrête pas de s'assoir a ma place.
And she touched my food.
Elle a touché ma nourriture.
Okay. yes. I took her clothes. but she started it.
Oui, j'ai pris ses habits, mais c‘est elle qui a commencé.
No. that's not fair.
Non, ce n‘est pas juste.
Why should I have to apologize?
Pourquoi faudrait-il que je m'excuse ?
I really don't think this is the kind of thing Jesus concerns himself with.
Je ne pense pas que ce soit le genre de choses qui préoccupe Jésus.
No. you're right. I don't really know what Jesus thinks about.
Tu as raison. Je ne sais pas ce que pense Jésus.
All right!
C‘est bon !
Goodbye.
Au revoir.
-Did you tell on me? -Are you kidding me?
- Tu as cafté ? - Ça va pas, non ?
I already have two strikes.
J'ai déja commis deux fautes.
I am very. very sorry for what I have done.
Je suis vraiment désolé pour ce que j'ai fait.
Here's your laundry.
Voilà ton linge.
l rescind your strikes and you are no longer banished.
J'efface tes trois fautes et tu n'es plus bannie.
Can I sit wherever I want?
Je peux m'assoir où je veux ?
Never mind. Never mind. That's not important.
Peu importe. Ce n‘est pas grave.
Sheldon. this was big of you.
Tu as fait un gros effort.
-Thank you. I really appreciate it. -Thank you.
- Merci beaucoup. - Merci.
-Good night. Sheldon. -Penny?
- Bonne nuit. - Penny ?
Well played.
Bien joué.
-Thank you. -Just remember...
- Merci. - Mais rappelle-toi,
...with great power comes great responsibility.
les grands pouvoirs s'accompagnent de grandes responsabilités.
Understood.
Compris.
Can I help you?
Je peux vous aider ?
Yes. we're here to fix the cable.
On Vient réparer le câble.
I think we have satellite.
Je crois qu'on a le satellite.
That's what I meant.
C‘est ce que je voulais dire.
She's taller than all the women in my family combined.
Elle est plus grande que toutes les femmes de ma famille mises bout a bout.
What do we do now?
On fait quoi ?
Follow Mrs. Wolowitz.
On suit Mme Wolowitz.
[ENGLISH SDH]
[FRENCH]